needfreerecharge.com 2016-11-26

# Privacy Policy - Need Free Recharge

Here, The word “We” Refer to the website www.needfreerecharge.com

**Why we collect information** ** **

1) To run and operate our webiste

2) To improve users experience to our websites

3) So that in case of any dispute your information can be used

### Personal Information

We may collect personal identification information from visitors/Users when they register at needfreerecharge.com Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they submit such information to us by their choice. In addition, users can always ignore/refuse to provide us personal information.  
We also collect email addresses for communication purposes only.  
Needfreerecharge.com does not trade, sell, deal your Personal Information with anyone.

### Non-Personal Information

We may collect non-personal information about Users when they visit our site. It may include the browser name, the type of computers, operating system and the Internet service providers.

### Cookies

Our Website use cookies to enhance User experience.  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive.User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies. If they do so, it may affect overall experience with us.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on trickloot.com. Google’s DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.needfreerecharge.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.  
Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Amazon  
Flipkart  
Snapdeal

### **How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### **Children’s privacy**

Visitor must be at least 21 years old to use our site. If you are below 15 years of age, you are strictly prohibited from registering on our Website.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

We  have the right to update this privacy policy at any time. However, You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy from time to time and become aware of any changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or any query please contact us using via our contact page
